https://brantfestival.bc.ca/privacy-policy/

Introduction
This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for The Brant Wildlife Festival website. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website (brantfestival.bc.ca).
The sponsor of this website, The Nature Trust of British Columbia (naturetrust.bc.ca), is committed to protecting the privacy of everyone with whom we interact. Any use or disclosure of personal information is subject to consent.
Personal Information
We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. If you contact us or voluntarily submit photos to our album, we will collect your email address and name. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfil your request.
Your Access to Personal Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via info@naturetrust.bc.ca or at 604.924.9771:
See what data we have about you, if any.Change / correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concerns you have about our use of your data.
Privacy Practices
Personal information gathered by this website is kept in strict confidence. Safeguards are in place to ensure that the information is not disclosed or shared more widely than is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was gathered. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Our website contains links to other websites that may be subject to varying privacy standards. Neither this website nor The Nature Trust of BC assume any responsibility for the privacy practices, policies and actions of the third parties that operate these websites.
Cookies and Pixel Tags
Like many other websites, we use cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to better understand how our website is used, to make sure our information is displayed correctly, and to improve the performance of our website for our users, particularly the way search pages are delivered. The Nature Trust does not use cookies to retain personal information about users of this website, and we do not sell information about traffic patterns.
This website may use pixel tags to track the actions of users of our website, measure the success of marketing campaigns, and compile statistics (such as response rates) about the use of this website.
We will never use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our website. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we (nor Google will link), or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this website with any personally identifiable information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. If you think we are not abiding by this Privacy Policy, you should contact us immediately at info@naturetrust.bc.ca or call 604.924.9771
Last updated December 7, 2018
Home
About
Blog
Links
Privacy Policy
Contact
© 2018 Brant Wildlife Festival.
This website is sponsored by The Nature Trust of BC
©  2020 . Built using WordPress and the Mesmerize Theme
